enjoymmo.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy

Ingle Games Privacy Policy:

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Ingle Games Ltd. websites. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

We collect the following information:

\- User ID: To identify yourself and access your account information  
\- Password: To protect your account and account information  
\- ZIP Code: To process billing information when purchasing items using credit.   
\- Country: Some of our games are not available in countries where other publishers own the distribution rights. We use the - Country to allow access to our games, also for billing purposes when purchasing items that require credit information  
\- Birthday: To validate the age to comply with COPA rules and to process billing information when purchasing items that require credit.  
\- Valid Email address: We collect the email to validate account information to access systems and game. You can use the email to retrieve your User ID if you have forgotten it. We will never give out or sale your email or mailing list information to 3rd party companies, for the activities of mass mailing or advertising.   
\- Character name:  Used for the purposes of dealing with MWO employees and account information.  
\- IP Address: Each and every time you log on your IP address will be collected in order to protect you in case someone other than you is using your account.   
\- Cookies: We store cookies on your PC to keep track of your Account and it is not shared with other companies.

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. Once you've clicked on an advertisement and have left our Website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their site. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

When purchasing game items or subscriptions to our games, you will have the choice to pay by Paypal, or any other e-commerce available today or in the future. We will collect the required information for each payment method; however, this information will be kept confidential and is only shared under industry standard security methodologies to the billing partners. The billing partners have no right to use your information other than completing the billing process you have initiated. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Our Commitment to Children's Privacy: 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. When a child under 18 years of age signs up we will not collect the Email address without the permission of the Parent or Legal Guardian and we will collect the other items listed above. We do not collect anything else. If a child under 18 years of age wants to post information on our website or chat with other players, we will require that they do not disclose any personal information such as the real name, address, phone number and anything that can be used to contact the child.

We ask that you educate your child to never give out email, name, address, and phone or pager information without parents consent. Tell them to always notify a parent OR guardians, when they feel threatened, or are asked for any personal information.

Our Commitment to Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. For visitors to our website, we look at the IP address to decide if we can grant access. We may deny access to identified violators of our terms of use, those who violated our privacy policies and those from countries we do not have rights to publish some of our games. We keep every IP address in a log file that is also used for marketing research.

How You Can Access or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by accessing your account or by filling out the proper forms on the Official Website. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.   

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We will disclose personal information when we believe in good faith that such disclosures are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena, or will help to enforce our Terms of Use; enforce contest, sweepstakes, promotions, and/or game rules; protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or, protect the safety and security of our Web sites.

How to Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, send us an email at support[AT]enjoymmo.com
